♪♪♪
- I JUST WANT TO ASK
THE QUESTION
WHO REALLY CARES?
TO SAVE A WORLD IN DESPAIR
♪♪♪
WHO REALLY CARES?
(IT FOLLOWS A WATER
CRISIS IN FLINT...
THAT BEGAN FOUR YEARS AGO
WHEN THE CITY STARTED DRAWING
WATER FROM THE FLINT RIVER,
EXPOSING THOUSANDS OF
PEOPLE TO THE TOXIC METAL)
[MARVIN SINGING] MOTHER, MOTHER
THERE'S TOO MANY OF YOU CRYING
[BABY TALK]
BROTHER, BROTHER, BROTHER
[POLICE CAR SIREN]
[POLICE RADIO VOICE] 25,
IT'S GONNA BE A BLACK MALE
IN A WHITE T-SHIRT...)
THERE'S FAR TOO MANY
OF YOU DYING
(HE'S RUNNING TOWARD QUIK TRIP)
[MALE VOICE] 14 MILLION
MORE AMERICANS
YOU KNOW WE'VE GOT
TO FIND A WAY
(WOULD BE UNINSURED NEXT YEAR)
(THIS DEADLY MASS SHOOTING...)
TO BRING SOME LOVIN'
HERE TODAY
(HAPPENED IN PARKLAND
FLORIDA AT...)
♪ YEAH ♪
(MARJORY STONEMAN
DOUGLASS HIGH SCHOOL)
♪ FATHER, FATHER
[VOCALIZING] ♪
♪ WE DON'T NEED TO ESCALATE ♪
♪ YOU SEE, WAR IS
NOT THE ANSWER ♪
[POLICE CAR RADIO VOICE]
♪ FOR ONLY LOVE
CAN CONQUER HATE
(OH OH OH) ♪
♪ YOU KNOW WE'VE
GOT TO FIND A WAY (OH OH OH) ♪
♪ TO BRING SOME LOVIN'
HERE TODAY, (OH OH OH) ♪
♪ PICKET LINES
AND PICKET SIGNS ♪
♪ DON'T PUNISH ME
WITH BRUTALITY ♪
♪ TALK TO ME,
SO YOU CAN SEE ♪
♪ OH, WHAT'S GOING ON
(WHAT'S GOING ON) ♪
♪ WHAT'S GOING ON
♪ YEAH, WHAT'S GOING ON
(WHAT'S GOING ON) ♪
♪ AH, WHAT'S GOING ON
[VOCALIZING]
♪ RIGHT ON, BABY ♪
[PROTESTING VOICES]
♪ RIGHT ON BROTHER ♪
♪ RIGHT ON BABE ♪
[VOCALIZING]
♪ MOTHER, MOTHER ♪
♪ EVERYBODY THINKS WE'RE WRONG ♪
[VOCALIZING]
♪ OH, BUT WHO ARE
THEY TO JUDGE US ♪
♪ SIMPLY 'CAUSE
OUR HAIR IS LONG ♪
♪ OH, YOU KNOW WE'VE
GOT TO FIND A WAY ♪
[VOCALIZING]
♪ TO BRING SOME
UNDERSTANDING HERE TODAY ♪
♪ OH OH OH ♪
♪ PICKET LINES ♪
[VOCALIZING]
♪ AND PICKET SIGNS ♪
♪ DON'T PUNISH ME
WITH BRUTALITY ♪
♪ C'MON TALK TO ME ♪
♪ SO YOU CAN SEE ♪
♪ WHAT'S GOING ON ♪
♪ YEAH, WHAT'S GOING ON ♪
♪ TELL ME WHAT'S GOING ON ♪
♪ I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT'S GOING ON ♪
[VOCALIZING]
♪ RIGHT ON BABY,
RIGHT ON BABY ♪
[VOCALIZING]
[PROTESTING VOICES]
♪ RIGHT ON BABY,
RIGHT ON BABY ♪
[PROTESTING VOICES]
[VOCALIZING]
[CHANTING]
♪ I WANT TO KNOW ♪
♪ WHAT'S GOING ON BABY ♪
♪♪♪
♪ YES I WANT TO KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON RIGHT NOW PEOPLE ♪